http://www.culver.edu/privacy

Home
Menu
AcademicsFuture StudentsCurrent StudentsAlumniParentsAthleticsGive
Search
Search
Homeprivacy
Privacy Notice
Culver-Stockton College takes your privacy seriously.  We want you to understand what information we collect and how we use it.At Culver-Stockton College, we care about providing you with information to manage and protect your online privacy. In compliance with the privacy provisions of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, we have developed this privacy policy to inform you about what information this website collects, who may receive that information, and what we may do with the information. In the following privacy notice, C-SC is referred to as “we” or “us.”Collection of Personal InformationCulver-Stockton College collects personal information to make our web services customizable for each user. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes your operating system and Internet browser. Our web server additionally records usage of pages by our visitors. We retain this information for research reports, and sometimes use this information so that we may improve the design and content of our website.Some of Culver-Stockton College's websites and services collect personally identifiable information to further adapt to our website visitors' needs. Some sites and services may require that you provide personally identifiable information in order to participate.  A person may voluntarily provide Culver-Stockton College with personal information via this website in a case where a user chooses to submit an online form. Online forms may be submitted for reasons such as
Applying to Culver-Stockton College
Requesting information through an inquiry form
Providing information about your transactions with us or others (including transactions with nonaffiliated third parties, school, guarantors, lenders, the U.S. Department of Education and as otherwise authorized by your promissory/Master Promissory Note(s)
Information we receive from third parties such as consumer reporting agencies
Your information will never be shared, given, or sold to a third party without your express consent. However, Culver-Stockton College may release personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of Culver-Stockton College staff, faculty, students, applicants or alumni.
How Culver-Stockton College Protects Your InformationWe have put in place appropriate software, hardware, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.If any changes are made to the privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Questions and ConcernsIf you have any questions about this privacy policy, or the content or practices of our website, you may contact the Culver-Stockton College Webmaster:webstuff@culver.edu.
Quick Links
Calendar
Directory
Campus Life
Majors
Virtual Tour
Quick Links
Calendar
Sitemap
The mission of Culver-Stockton College is to prepare students of promise for a dynamic world through our distinctive experiential curriculum within a supportive learning community founded upon the best values of faith and the human spirit.
© Copyright 2017 Culver-Stockton College, All rights reserved. Privacy Notice
©
